[
  { "question": "head (n)\n /hed/", "answer": "đầu" },
  { "question": "hair (n)\n /her/", "answer": "tóc" },
  { "question": "face (n)\n /feɪs/", "answer": "gương mặt" },
  { "question": "forehead (n)\n /ˈfɔː.rɪd/", "answer": "trán" },
  { "question": "eyebrow (n)\n /ˈaɪ.braʊ/", "answer": "lông mày" },
  { "question": "eye (n)\n /aɪ/", "answer": "mắt" },
  { "question": "eyelash (n)\n /ˈaɪ.læʃ/", "answer": "lông mi" },
  { "question": "nose (n)\n /noʊz/", "answer": "mũi" },
  { "question": "ear (n)\n /ɪr/", "answer": "tai" },
  { "question": "cheek (n)\n /tʃiːk/", "answer": "má" },
  { "question": "beard (n)\n /bɪrd/", "answer": "râu" },
  { "question": "mouth (n)\n /maʊθ/", "answer": "miệng" },
  { "question": "lip (n)\n /lɪp/", "answer": "môi" },
  { "question": "tooth (teeth)\n (n)\n /tuːθ/ /tiːθ/", "answer": "răng" },
  { "question": "gum (n)\n /ɡʌm/", "answer": "nướu, lợi" },
  { "question": "jaw (n)\n /dʒɔː/", "answer": "hàm, quai hàm" },
  { "question": "chin (n)\n /tʃɪn/", "answer": "cằm" },
  { "question": "neck (n)\n /nek/", "answer": "cổ" },
  { "question": "chest (n)\n /tʃest/", "answer": "ngực (chung)\n" },
  { "question": "back (n)\n /bæk/", "answer": "lưng" },
  { "question": "belly (n)\n /ˈbeli/", "answer": "bụng" },
  { "question": "hip (n)\n /hɪp/", "answer": "hông" },
  { "question": "arm (n)\n /ɑːrm/", "answer": "cánh tay" },
  { "question": "armpit (n)\n /ˈɑːrm.pɪt/", "answer": "nách" },
  { "question": "forearm (n)\n /ˈfɔː.rɑːrm/", "answer": "cẳng tay" },
  { "question": "elbow (n)\n /ˈel.boʊ/", "answer": "khuỷu tay" },
  { "question": "finger (n)\n /ˈfɪŋ.ɡɚ/", "answer": "ngón tay" },
  { "question": "knuckle (n)\n /ˈnʌk.əl/", "answer": "khớp đốt ngón tay" },
  { "question": "leg (n)\n /leɡ/", "answer": "chân" },
  { "question": "knee (n)\n /niː/", "answer": "đầu gối" },
  { "question": "ankle (n)\n /ˈæŋ.kəl/", "answer": "mắt cá chân" },
  { "question": "heel (n)\n /hiːl/", "answer": "gót chân" }
]
